<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="form.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"
?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="form.css"?>
<tei xml:space="preserve">
	<teiHeader>
		<fileDesc xml:id=""/>
	</teiHeader>
	<text>
		<body><form><name>D'ANNE TANT (Pierre</name>), <desc>né à Bruxelles. -6, <lb/>boulevard Michel-Brézin, Garches (S.</desc> <lb/></form><form><desc>-14, rue La</desc> <lb/></form><form><name>DANTU (Georges</name>), <desc>né à Paris. <lb/>Fontaine</desc></form><form><name>DAYNES (Victor</name>), <desc>né à Colmar. -115, rue Bo <lb/>livar</desc></form><form><name>DEBIESSE (Philippe</name>), <desc>né à Villefranche (Rhône). <lb/>Avenue du Chemin-de-Fer, Raincy</desc></form><form><name>EEBRAUX (René</name>), <desc>né en France. -18, rue d'Ar <lb/>menonville, Neuilly</desc></form><form><name>DEBRIE (Gustave</name>), <desc>né à Paris. -54, rue Lho <lb/>mond, 5e</desc></form><form><name>DEFONTAINE (Rodolphe</name>), <desc>né à Arras. -43, rue <lb/>Lepic</desc></form><form><desc>-8, place de la</desc> <lb/></form><form><name>DEFONTE (Edmond</name>), <desc>né à Paris. <lb/>Mairie, Fontenay-aux-Roses (Seine)</desc></form><form><name>DEKEN (Mme Marthe de</name>), <desc>née à Paris. -14, place <lb/>Dauphine, 1er</desc></form><form><name>DELACOUR (J.-Mathieu</name>), <desc>né à Paris. -3, rue <lb/>Dutot, 15e</desc></form><form><name>DELACROIX (Paul</name>), <desc>né à Paris.. -38, rue Fes <lb/>sart, 19e</desc></form><form><name>DELAMARRE DE MONCHAUX (Marcel</name>), <desc>né à <lb/>Paris. -212 ter, boulevard Pereire</desc></form><form><name>DELAPORTE (Engène</name>), <desc>né à Vensaillès. -2; rue <lb/>de la Paroisse, Versailles</desc></form><form><name>DELAUNAY</name>, <desc>né à Bris. -3, rue des Grands <lb/>gustins, 6e</desc></form><form><name>DELCUS (Louis</name>), <desc>né à Lillers (Pas <lb/>23, rue de Maubeuge, 9e</desc></form><form><name>DELESTRE (Eugène</name>), <desc>né à Paris. -11, rue des <lb/>Sablons, 16e</desc></form><form><name>DELFOSSE (L.-B.</name>), <desc>né à Bayonne. -22, rue Saint <lb/>Augustin, 2e</desc></form><form><name>SAINT-DELIS (Henri de</name>), <desc>né à Hesdin. -8, rue <lb/>Emile-Zola, Le Havre</desc></form><form><name>SAINT-DELIS (René de</name>), <desc>né à Saint-Omer. -8, <lb/>rue Emile-Zola, Le Havre</desc></form><form><name>DELOISON (Roger</name>), <desc>né à Paris. -10, rue Dela <lb/>bordère, Neuilly</desc> <lb/></form><form><name>DELORME-CORNET (Mme Louise</name>), <desc>née à Lyon. <lb/>11, rue des Sablons, 16e</desc></form><form><name>DELTOMBE (Paul</name>), <desc>né à Catillon (Nord). -49, <lb/>rue Beaunier, 14e</desc></form><form><name>DELUC (Gabriel</name>), <desc>né à Saint-Jean-de-Luz. -9, rue <lb/>Falguière, 15e</desc></form><form><name>DEMAILLY (Louis</name>), <desc>né à Maroeuil (Pas <lb/>6, rue Armand-Gauthier, 18e</desc></form><form><name>DEMAN (Paule</name>), <desc>née à Bruxelles. -« La Lézar <lb/>dière », Le Lavandou (Var)</desc></form><form><name>DEMARLE (Alexis</name>), <desc>né à Tombouctou. -54, rue <lb/>Lamartine, 9e</desc>. <lb/></form><form><name>DENAYER (Félix</name>), <desc>né à Ixelles (Belgique). -33, <lb/>rue du Dragon, 6e</desc></form><form><name>DENISSE (J.-Jean</name>), <desc>né à Bordeaux. -16, rue <lb/>C.-Souplet, Saint-Quentin (Aisne</desc>)</form><form><name>DÉOM (Louis</name>), <desc>né à Paris. -4, rue du Roi <lb/>Sicile, 4e</desc></form><form><name>DERUET (Raymonde</name>), <desc>née à Paris. -12, rue <lb/>Bréa, 6e</desc></form><form><name>DESCABISSAC (Félice</name>), <desc>né à Vienne. -Fag <lb/>Ober-Osterreich (Au <lb/>werkerstr. 17, Gmunden, <lb/>triche)</desc></form><form><name>DESHAYES (Frédéric</name>), <desc>né à Paris. -190, rue <lb/>Marcadet, 18e</desc></form></body>
	</text>
</tei>
