<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="form.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"
?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="form.css"?>
<tei xml:space="preserve">
	<teiHeader>
		<fileDesc xml:id=""/>
	</teiHeader>
	<text>
		<body><form><name>AUTHIER (Mlle), Henriette</name>, <desc>née à Moulins (Allier). -<lb/>7, rue de l'Oiseau, Moulins</desc></form><form><name>BAHUET, Alfred-Louis</name>, <desc>né à Paris. -61, rue Monsieur <lb/>le</desc> <lb/></form><form><name>BARABANDY, Richard</name>, <desc>né à Milan (Italie). -34, bou <lb/>levard de Clichy, Paris</desc></form><form><name>BARBIER, Ernest</name>, <desc>né à Chartres. -131, rue de Fon <lb/>tenay. Vincennes</desc></form><form><name>BARON (Mme), Hélène (Française)</name>. -<desc>Villa Sainte <lb/>Rose, Petit-Juas, Cannes</desc></form><form><name>BASTON, Alexandre</name>, <desc>né à Paris. -Luzarches</desc></form><form><name>BATTAGLLA, Matteo</name>, <desc>né à Nice. -5, rue Bernard <lb/>Palissy. Paris</desc></form><form><name>BAUQUIER, Jules</name>, <desc>né à Paris. -<lb/>26, rue du Roi <lb/>Sicile</desc></form><form><name>BELLANGER, Auguste</name>, <desc>né à Villette (Seine <lb/>7, rue Denfert-Rochereau, Paris</desc></form><form><name>BENOIST, Théophile-Maximilien</name>, <desc>né à Paris. -44, <lb/>Passage des Thermopyles</desc></form><form><name>BERCIOUX, Jean-Charles</name>, <desc>né à Paris. -51 bis rue <lb/>Cler</desc></form><form><name>BERNARD, Emile-Henry</name>, <desc>né à Lille en-Flandre. -5, <lb/>avenue Beaulieu, Asnières</desc></form><form><name>BERNARD, Lucien-Saint-Fargeau-Eugène</name>, <desc>né à Paris. <lb/>28, rue du Lycée, Sceaux (Seine)</desc></form><form><name>BERTHIER, Paul</name>, <desc>né à Paris, -13, rue Bonaparte</desc></form><form><name>BERTIE (Mlle), Fanny</name>, <desc>née à Londres. -47, rue Lau <lb/>gier, Paris</desc></form><form><name>BESSET, Cyrille</name>, <desc>né à Saint-Sernin-du-Plain (Saône <lb/>Loire. -Villa Lucie, Nice</desc></form><form><name>BESNUS, Georges</name>, <desc>né à Paris. <lb/>8, rue Notre <lb/>des</desc> <lb/></form><form><name>BIDERMANN, Jean</name>, <desc>né à l'Ile Bourbon. -32, rue de <lb/>Cléry. Paris</desc></form><form><name>BLANMANGIN, Paul</name>, <desc>né à Paris. <lb/>2, Place de Bitche</desc></form><form><name>BOCH (Mlle), Anna</name>, <desc>née à Bruxelles. <lb/>2, avenue de <lb/>laToison d'or (Bruxelles)</desc></form><form><name>BOISTEL, Léo</name>, <desc>né à Dieupentale (Tarn-et-Garonne). -<lb/>Dieupentale</desc></form><form><name>BOITELET, (Mlle) Marie-Louise</name>, <desc>née à Guéret. -34, <lb/>rue Fontaine, Paris</desc></form><form><name>BONNAFFÉ, Jules</name>, <desc>né à Bordeaux (Gironde). -<lb/>52, avenue du Roule, Néuilly</desc> <lb/></form><form><name>BONNARD, Pierre</name>, <desc>né à Paris. -28, rue Pigalle</desc>. <lb/></form><form><name>BOU-CHAKOUR, Marc</name>, <desc>né à Paris. -Le Puy (Hte</desc> <lb/></form><form><name>BOUDIER (Mme), Jeanne</name>, <desc>née à Paris, 16, rue Jeanne <lb/>Hachette</desc></form><form><name>BOURDAIS [Mlle), Julienne</name>, <desc>née à Poissy (Seine <lb/>Oise)</desc></form><form><name>BOUSSENOT, Fernand</name>, <desc>né à Paris. -5, rue Lincoln</desc></form><form><name>BOUVET, Henry-Marius-Camille,</name> <desc>né à Lyon. -75, ave <lb/>nue de Wagram</desc> <lb/></form><form><name>BRANDT, Pierre</name>, <desc>né à Paris. -A l'Ile Saint</desc> <lb/></form><form><name>BRESSANT, Paul</name>, <desc>né à la Basse-Terre (Guadeloupe). <lb/>174, avenue du Maine</desc></form></body>
	</text>
</tei>
