<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="form.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"
?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="form.css"?>
<tei xml:space="preserve">
	<teiHeader>
		<fileDesc xml:id=""/>
	</teiHeader>
	<text>
		<body><form><name>LECLERCQ, Théodore</name>, <desc>né à Oresmaux (Somme) <lb/>10, rue du Regard. Paris</desc></form><form><name>LEFEBVRE-LOURDET, Maurice</name>, <desc>né à Paris. -82, bou <lb/>levard de Clichy</desc></form><form><name>LEGUAY, Charles-Henri</name>, <desc>né à Paris. -29, rue de Turin</desc></form><form><name>LEJEUNE, Edouard-Angel</name>, <desc>né à Caen (Calvados) <lb/>26, rue des Jardies, à Bellevue (Seine</desc> <lb/></form><form><name>LEMMEN, Georges</name>. -<desc>220, rue Verte, Bruxelles</desc></form><form><name>LESSORE, Henri-Emile</name>, <desc>né à Paris. -2, quai de <lb/>Gesvres, atelier 21, quai Bourbon</desc></form><form><name>LE VILLAIN, Auguste-Ernest</name>, <desc>né à Paris. -30, rue <lb/>Alphonse</desc> <lb/></form><form><name>LHUER, Jules-Jean</name>, <desc>né à Paris. -4, rue Las</desc> <lb/></form><form><name>LOMBARD, Gaëtan</name>, <desc>né à Paris -32, rue Caumartin</desc></form><form><name>LORIN, Georges</name>, <desc>né à Auxerre (Vonne). -7, rue <lb/>Campagne-Première, Paris</desc></form><form><name>LOTTIN, Frédérick-A</name>. -<desc>42, rue Boulainvilliers, Passy</desc></form><form><name>LUCE, Maximilien</name>, <desc>né à Paris. -6, rue Cortot</desc> <lb/></form><form><name>LYONNET, Henri</name>, <desc>né à Dornecy (Nièvie). -17, rue <lb/>de Madrid. Paris</desc></form><form><name>MADIOL, Adrien-Jean</name>, <desc>né à Groningen (Hollande). <lb/>Plaine des Tilleuls, Wolunée Saint</desc> <lb/></form><form><name>MAILLARD, Th.</name>, <desc>né à Chatellerault. -12, rue du <lb/>Cognet, Chatellerault (Vienne</desc></form><form><name>MAISONNEUVE, Paul</name>, <desc>né à Tours. -22, rue Ganne <lb/>ron, Paris</desc></form><form><name>MALASSEZ (Mme), Jeanne</name>, <desc>née à Paris. -168, Boule <lb/>vard Saint</desc> <lb/></form><form><name>MALVAL (de), Edouard</name>, <desc>né à Lyon. -18 rue Molitor, <lb/>Paris</desc></form><form><name>MANGIN, Marcel</name>, <desc>né à Cherbourg. -130, boulevard <lb/>Haussmann, Paris</desc></form><form><name>MARC (Mme) Mathilde</name>, <desc>née à Bordeaux (Gironde). <lb/>-14, rue Clapeyron, Paris</desc></form><form><name>MATHIEU (Mlle) Marie-Alexandrine</name>, <desc>née à Nevers (Niè <lb/>vre). -Marry, près Nevers (Nièvre</desc></form><form><name>MAUFRA, Maxime</name>, <desc>né à Nantes. -3 bis rue Bleue</desc></form><form><name>MAZADE (de), Alexandre</name>, <desc>né à Paris. -107, boule <lb/>vard Sébastopol</desc></form><form><name>MEIFREN, Eliseo</name>, <desc>né à Barcelone (Espagne). -15, rue <lb/>Hégésippe</desc> <lb/></form><form><name>MERCIER, Paul-Joseph-Marie</name>, <desc>né à Dreux (Eure <lb/>Loir). <lb/>37, rue Denfert-Rochereau, Paris</desc></form><form><name>MESPLÈS, Paul-Eugène</name>, <desc>né à Paris. -29, rue Clauzel</desc></form><form><name>MESUREUR, Noé</name>, <desc>né à Boulogne-sur-Mer. -9, rue <lb/>Clausel, Pariset à Cucy par Etaples</desc></form><form><name>MEUNIÉ, Paul-Henri</name>, <desc>né à Paris. -15, boulevard <lb/>Berthier</desc></form><form><name>MICHON, Edouard-Michel</name>, <desc>né à Anet (Eure <lb/>Anet</desc></form><form><name>MILLET, James</name>, <desc>né à Genève (Suisse) (Français) <lb/>123, boulevard Richard-Lenoir, Paris</desc></form><form><name>MONIER, Camille</name>, <desc>né à Montpellier. -12, rue des <lb/>Artistes, Paris</desc></form><form><name>MOREL, Victor</name>, <desc>né à Paris. -32, rue Saint</desc> <lb/></form><form><name>MORET, Henry</name>, <desc>né à Cherboueg. -Chez M. Blan <lb/>chet, 20, rue Saint-Benoist, Paris</desc></form></body>
	</text>
</tei>
